(Sheldon:)-But you don't even know...
-Doesn't matter.
-But, now, but in my defense--
(Sheldon:)You're not listening
to my side of it.
(Penny:)Okay, fine, Sheldon.
What is your side?
(Sheldon:)Well--
(Penny:)Nope, got to go with Amy on this one.
The shrimp was spicy.
You want a TUNIS?
(Howard:)You got the tropical fruit kind?
(Raj:)No, if I buy those,
I just go through them like candy.
(Howard:)Tell me about it. One time, I swear
I pooped out a stick of chalk.
(Howard:)-I'll get it.
-Thanks.
(Penny:)-Hi.
-Hi.
(Bernadette:)I may have overreacted.
(Howard:)Well, I didn't handle it
so great, either.
(Bernadette:)It's just sometimes I feel like
you enjoy spending time
(Bernadette:)with your friends more than with me.
(Howard:)-That's not true.
-It's not?
(Bernadette:)You spend all day together at work,
(Bernadette:)and then you all hang out at night
playing games,
(Bernadette:)going to the comic book store.
(Bernadette:)Last week, you two got
8 couples massage.